(Leonard:)- Hey.
- Oh, hey. You work the lunch shift?
Yeah. Got 8 pounds of salmon
that's about to go bad.
(Penny:)- Do you know how to cook it?
- Not really.
(Penny:)Damn it.
Should've liberated the iffy chicken.
So, what are you
and Professor Fussyface up to tonight?
(Leonard:)Star Wars on Blu-ray.
(Penny:)Haven't you seen that movie
a thousand times?
(Leonard:)Not on Blu-ray.
(Leonard:)Only twice on Blu-ray.
Oh, Leonard. Ugh.
(Leonard:)I know. It's high-resolution sadness.
Well, I was gonna take myseIf out
to a movie tonight.
You wanna go?
- Really? Do we do that?
- What do you mean?
(Leonard:)You know, we haven't spent time alone
together since we broke up.
(Penny:)It's not a date, Leonard.
It's a man and a woman hanging out...
(Penny:)...not having sex
at the end of the night.
(Leonard:)Sounds like most of my dates.
(Sheldon(off, voice heard through apartment door as they approach):)Oh, dear Lord.
Get away from me, you monster.